Every dream begins with a single step
The Walk is a history, drama, adventure film directed by Robert Zemeckis.
The story of French high-wire artist Philippe Petit's attempt to
cross the Twin Towers of the World Trade Center in 1974.
Philippe Petit, played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Papa Rudy, played by Ben Kingsley.
Annie Allix, played by Charlotte Le Bon.
J.P., played by James Badge Dale.
Jean-Louis, played by Clément Sibony.
Jeff / Jean-François, played by César Domboy.
The Walk is a 2015 American biographical drama film directed by Robert
Zemeckis, who co-wrote the screenplay with Christopher Browne.
It is based on the story of French high-wire artist Philippe Petit's walk
between the Twin Towers of the World Trade Center in 1974.
The film stars Joseph Gordon-Levitt as Petit, alongside Ben Kingsley, Charlotte
Le Bon, James Badge Dale, Ben Schwartz, and Steve Valentine.
Following its premiere at the New York Film Festival, The Walk was released by TriStar Pictures on
September 30, 2015 in the United States in IMAX 3D, and on October 9 in regular 2D and 3D.
It received positive reviews from critics and grossed $61 million worldwide.
The film is dedicated to the victims of the September 11 attacks.
The film explores themes of new york city, skyscraper,
1970s, biography, based on true story.
The tone is emotional.